Thank you for watching!
This team doesn't have the nuance of having fun live and involving the audience.
I think that's the biggest issue.
We've been here for 3 months, but we don't have any freshness.
Naru-nan, you didn't do this before, right?
It's so fresh, look at them.
And you're not very good at it, in a good way or a bad way.
I think that's a good thing.
On the other hand, the groups that have been doing this for a long time are so good that they're too banal.
It's like a cloak.
I don't know, I don't think there's a good balance there.
You need to separate the cool parts a little bit more.
Everything is cool, and it's too much work.
You have to have more light fun and more fun.
I should think about the balance a little bit more.
Yes, I think so.
You seem to be having the most fun.
You know, it would be best if all of them were like that.
It's not about technique. Charm is the best.
There are a lot of people who have a lot of skill but can't sell.
Attractiveness will never overtake technology, so it's definitely better to be attractive.
You should aim to be more attractive.
It's not about technique, singing, dancing, etc.
It's better to practice every day to bring out the best of yourself.
You dance and sing well in your own way.
The audience is looking for more than that when they see you.
I think that's the charm.
That's what you should study.
Yes, sir.
Enjoy the show.
I'll do my best.
Okay, thank you very much.
I'm done.
Thank you very much.
We have a single in the house.
I'm Nanako Ogawa.
I'm Ogawa.
I'm Nanako.
I am Nanako Ogawa.
I'm Nanako Ogawa.
There's a girl who went to the other side of the train and didn't come for an hour.
I found out today. She woke up very early today and went out with her mother.
She went out with her mother.
Is that what happened?
Yes, but it's not the same thing.
That's why,
I'm scared.
This is the ocean, right?
Let's get him out in the ocean.
That's great.
It's like a profile video. It's like a self-introduction video.
Nice, high quality scent of the sea.
A wonderful, wonderful aroma.
Wow, there's a seagull flying.
The birds are waiting.
The seagull is flying.
We all want to win.
Then please listen to me.
It's going to be dark soon.
Isn't that a bit intense?
There is also the issue of the good part.
If I tell them to smile and talk to each other,
We say it with a smile, so they don't say anything like that.
Like, "Yes.
If he nodded, it would make sense.
At the end, before we enter the room, do we say something one more time or not?
Clap, clap, clap, clap, clap, clap, clap, clap, clap, clap, clap, clap.
More!
Oh, that's good!
Nice to see you again!
Nice to see you again! I'm Kandichu!
Let's start enjoying the second half.
The model of a model of a model of a model of a model of a model of a model is the beginning story.
First, we have a sambun juku paper lying down, then an Italian chestnut mont blanc, and then a keepy-core gold ,
And a pack of 6 fresh scones as a snack. Best regards.
It's gross, right?
It's pretty gross.
This will help with my general tiredness and lethargy.
Yes, I'll have some. I'll take it.
Gross.
Gross. Gross.
I'm glad.
I'm sorry. I got on the wrong side. I'm sorry I got on the wrong side.
You can see the rehearsal.
Thank you very much.
Oh, no, no.
Yes, we're done.
It's over!
Yes, sir. Good work!
Good morning.
I'll be back in Yokohama when I realize it.
It's already in the past.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry to bother you on such a bad day.
It's Mocchan!
He's alive!I'm alive.
Alive.
Fighting hairy.
Fighting hairsies.
I just made a really weird face.
BTOB
Come on, the whole thing.
Because I want to see your boy.
Candy Tune. Please take care of the rehearsal.
Please take care of us.
Then I would like you to start with the first song, CATCH YOU.
I want you to remember, help me 办경 against any blue
Kinder
Hello again, my name is Candy Tune.
Are you enjoying this special stage just for today?
Please accept our 7 members' wishes.
Let's enjoy the second half of the show.
The story of the beginning with 7 members
Seven Color Prologue
A Story of One Person's Time
Why is this so bad?
I'm wearing a torch, aren't I?
I'll give it to you.
Greetings from the first row.
Okay.
Then it's more than a candy tune rehearsal.
I look forward to working with you on the show.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for the rehearsal.
I want you to get ready to go home and practice.
Okay.
Thank you very much.
We worked really hard all the time to prepare for the event, and almost every day we had a line with only the members working late at night or late at night after the lesson,
I hope I can show those efforts.
But Mizuki, you have never really won in all the competitions. I've never won a competition.
That's why I want to win.
It would be my first victory.
I really want to make this a fun concert for everyone. Let's have fun!
I eat a lot when I'm anxious, but I'm eating a lot.
I really felt that there are so many people supporting us in places we don't know, even people we have never met before,
They are supporting us in many ways that we can't even see,
I really thought that I have to enjoy myself today, but I also felt that I have to win.
I'm going to have fun!
I've received so many warm messages of support from the people who have been involved in this event,
I'm really looking forward to it after seeing the warm messages of support from those who have been involved in the event, and the tweets from candy customers who said they would be at the venue,
The result will come anyway, so I want to enjoy the show without any regrets.
I'm looking forward to it. Ame-chan! Thank you very much for watching the live streaming every day for a week until today.
I will do my best in today's live so that I have no regrets, so I hope everyone will give me lots and lots of support.
I'm going to the men's stage for sure! I'm looking forward to it!
I'm looking forward to performing in front of 1,500 people, so I'm going to enjoy myself.
I told everyone not to be nervous because if everyone is nervous, it will reflect on me.
Yes, we are here today thanks to Ame-chan, and we are desperate to be here,
I think that through this all-winning competition, Ame-chan has become Ame-chan, or rather, the CanCho team has become united.
I received a lot of love from everyone, and I would like to repay it in the future, so please continue to support us.
I love you!
I'm already feeling nervous to the max right now!
The tension that has been gradually rising since yesterday is now at its maximum. It's not good.
When I said I was nervous, Rinomaru got mad at me.
He told me to stop because he would be filmed.
I'm really, really nervous inside.
Even the members who say they are not nervous.
But I'm really happy that we made it this far,
Even if we lost today, we still have a lot to leave behind,
If we win, I think we will be able to see a lot of wonderful and fun scenery together again,
I will do my best to take everyone to a wonderful place.
I will do my best!
When I was delivering the message, there was a big ball behind me.
I saw a lot of messages written by the candy people for us.
I took a picture of it with my cell phone and read it while I was there today.
I took pictures of them on my cell phone and read them while I was there today.
I got a lot of nice words from them, and even during the delivery, some of them said that they would go to see the show.
I was so encouraged when she said that she'd be there to watch the show even during the streaming and that she'd support us on the streaming even if she couldn't go to the show.
Just by saying that, it means a lot to us to be able to participate in the "Zenkoku Senso".
I really felt that there was a meaning for us to participate in this battle.
Whatever the result is, I have no regrets for having done my best, so I hope you all will support us without any worries.
Thank you very much.
I caught a cold about a week ago, and I really couldn't speak yesterday and the day before.
I've been doing some silent treatment recently, I talked yesterday and the day before yesterday, but I'm getting better day by day and I'm feeling rather good now.
I'm recovering day by day, and I'm feeling better and better, so I'd like to do my best to show you all how well I'm doing.
But I'm not sure if I'm in over my head.
I'm not sure if I'll be able to handle it, but I'll do my best.
I hope that the candy customers and supporters who came today will say that they had a good time.
I'm going to enjoy myself most of all without any regrets.
Mamimemo mamomo machitsutetotato
We'll dance next to you.
Sleazy boy! I'll make him dance at the camp!
Oh, yeah?
Are you listening to the album?
We're close.
That's what I'm talking about. If you put the gradations with Erin on top of each other...
It's like the end of a road that goes on and on and on and on and on and on.
When it rains.
When it snows.When it snows
When it gets dark
I'm sure the light will be near
I'm too nervous. You know the daily gigs. I'm 70% nervous at my daily gigs, and this day I'm already 170% nervous.
More than double.
Why don't you just have fun at your gigs?
Have fun.
It's cuter to have fun than to be nervous.
I'm going to have fun.
I have to be careful.
I've got to be careful with dirt.
I'll remember to keep the connection.
And anything else is fine as long as you're having fun.
I'll be fine.
Having fun?
Let's find even one fan.
Yes, sir.
That time, that time.
You're looking forward to it, right?
Don't worry.
She's cute.
She's cute?
You're the cutest.
I have to say something today.
Why are you talking?
Let's be cheerful.
I'm fine.
Ready.
Dekaja dekaja dekaja dekaja dee!
Please do it.
Please.
Yes, please.
The camera will give you the most peace of mind.
Are you ready?
Yes, I'm fine.
The SE is about to start, isn't it?
It's starting.
Climb the stairs as high as you can.
We're ready.
Don't miss.
Ed.
Hello again, Candy Chain.
Are you enjoying our special stage just for today?
It's been three months since our debut. Please accept our passionate wishes.
A new story connected by 7 members
That's all for us, Candy June.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work.
The staff is cute.
Really cute.
They are so cute.
Soooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo all cute.
You enjoyed the wonderful live performance.
I could hear your voice.
I could hear it.
The MC was good.
It was good.
From the middle.
I was surprised in the middle.
It was fun.
I didn't do it this time.
What did you say?
That was great.
We did it.
I bit it.
I did it.
Please make sure to go to the different groups and get one 1-point and one 2-point ticket each.
Perfect.
I'm off.
I'm so excited.
I put it back on.
It's okay because the clothes are cute.
We're fine because our clothes are cute.
I don't care about the hairstyle.
Now that we have the results, we will announce them.
Yes, so the results of the distribution poll,
250 points to the first place winner, Icol.
And 200 points to Candy Tune in second place.
And 160 points to the third place winner, Belly Pad Tune.
Thank you very much.
Did you all have a good time?
I could really feel everyone's enthusiasm,
And we were really full of energy,
It was a great opportunity for us.
We will be making our debut 3 months from now,
We are going to get bigger and bigger,
We hope that everyone will come to our shows again and enjoy them.
Thank you very much for your time today.
We are now in 4th place, Candy Tune.
So, the two groups that will advance to the finals are Merry But Tune and I-Call.
Thank you very much.
Now I would like to ask each of the finalists one by one,Now, let me ask you a couple of questions one by one,
I would like to ask them about their future plans,
Candy Choo, you really gave a wonderful live performance with the birds.
How was it today?
Yes, it was great. We have been thinking about this day for 3 months,
I am very disappointed,
But I also feel that the bond with the fans has grown deeper during this period,
But I also feel that our bond with the fans has grown deeper, and with the members and the staff has also grown deeper.
Thank you so much to everyone involved for allowing us to participate on such a wonderful stage,
Thank you so much to everyone involved for letting us participate in such a wonderful stage.
And to those who came to the venue today,
Thank you very much for your votes.
We are going to get bigger and bigger,
We will do our best to become even bigger and better so that we can become an idol group that you are happy to support.
Please continue to support us.
Thank you very much.
Do you have any live performances planned for this month?
I have a solo show this month, but it is almost sold out,
I would be very happy if you could come to my next solo show.
So, it's time to get going.
Yes.
You were at TV Rubble.
on the main stage that was on MBC, which opened on August 4.
In the finals.
The main stage
Icon's music live.
Best regards
Good morning.
Simple gummy yan
Today we have a call stage
We're here to talk to you.
Thank you.
You did it.
But you know what?
You didn't like it.
I couldn't do it anymore.
You did your best.
Thank you very much.
We all hugged.
Thank you for your hard work.
I did what I had to do.
Thank you very much.
Next year you'll be a regular urchin, right?
I'll stand around as a regular urchin.
It's the coolest thing.
That's the coolest?
I did my best.
It's good for Aishin.
Yes, it is.
It's amazing.
We were surprised by that.
We'll be in great shape now.
So, there will be a solo show this month, too.
And it's sold out.
Well, we're doing well for now.
They're cute.
What's next?
Room for growth?
It's room for growth.
It's a room for growth.
Here we go. Ready.
I'm on a roll! We're on a roll! Great job!
Yay!
Good morning.